https://www.e-node.net/en/mentionslegales.html

Plugin Masters
AreaList ProPrintList ProInternet ToolKitCalendarSetSuperReport Pro
Development v17
4D Developer Standard4D Developer Professional4D Team Developer Professional - 2 Users4D Team Developer Expansion - 1 User
Deployment v17
4D Server - 2 Users4D Client Expansion4D Write Pro Expansion4D View Pro Expansion4D Web Application Expansion - Unlimited4D Web Services Expansion - Unlimited4D Web Application Expansion for 4D Client - Unlimited - 1 User4D Web Services Expansion for 4D Client - Unlimited - 1 User4D for OCI Expansion - 1 User4D ODBC Pro Expansion - 1 User4D SQL Desktop
4D v18
Development v18
4D Developer Standard4D Developer Professional4D Team Developer Expansion - 1 User4D Team Developer Professional - 2 Users
Deployment v18
4D Server - 2 Users4D Client Expansion4D Write Pro Expansion4D View Pro Expansion4D Web Application Expansion - Unlimited4D Web Services Expansion - Unlimited4D Web Application Expansion for 4D Client - Unlimited - 1 User4D Web Services Expansion for 4D Client - Unlimited - 1 User4D for OCI Expansion - 1 User4D ODBC Pro Expansion - 1 User4D SQL Desktop
PDF
PDF Printer 4D PluginPDF-ToolsPDF-XChange Standard PrinterPDF-XChange EditorPDF-XChange Editor PlusPDF-XChange PRO
Contact
Direct payment
>CalendarSet v6CalendarSet version 6 includes the original API (no change needed in your existing code) as well as the more recent property-based API and adds new features:
-> Year view
-> Calendar.app-like display
-> Separate scrolling of all-day events area in Day/Week views
-> Separate 64-bit build signed & notarized on Mac
-> 40 new properties
>AreaList Pro v10.4With thousands of users around the world AreaList Pro is the #1 best seller professional tool for 4D, used by most top developers and publishers.Its 50 commands and over 400 properties provide tremendous possibilities, far beyond native 4D and ListBoxes, to display fields or arrays and interact with the user, with full control over data entry and display.
>Internet ToolKit v4.3.3, v5.0.3, v6.0.3As of version 4.3, Internet ToolKit comes through 3 different channels, each matching a 4D version range and SSL context.- Versions 4.3 and 4.x above for use with 4D v14.4-4D v15 (including 4D v15R4), includes openSSL 1.1.1d- Version 5.x for use with 4D v16 (including v15R5) - 4D v17 (including 4D v17R4)- Version 6.x for use with 4D v17R5 and above, 64-bit only, does not contain openSSL (uses what is provided by 4D)5 (ITK v4.1), 4D v16, 4D v17 (ITK v4.2).
>SuperReport Pro v4.2.1SuperReport Pro Version 4 is compatible with 4D v16, v17 and above versions in 32-bit and 64-bit modes. It brings the new palette interface for all object properties.
>PrintList Pro v6.4PrintList Pro Version 6 includes 4D v16, v17 and above, 64-bit compatibility, MySQL direct access, use of all AreaList Pro relevant properties, new properties and new commands.
>PDF-XChange Editor v8Edit PDF files directly.
e-Node is committed to your privacy. This statement discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site, including what kind of information is collected and tracked, and with whom this information is shared.
Collection of Personal Information
In general, you can visit e-Node Web sites without giving any information about yourself. A user's visit is tracked with the logging of IP addresses and domain names, but the user remains anonymous. This process simply gives us an idea of where users are headed to within our site, and how long they remain there.
There are certain activities where we will ask you to voluntarily provide information about yourself. Such activities include downloading beta releases, subscribing to announcements and/or mailing lists, and purchasing software products, upgrades, or books online from our online Store. For some activities, you may be asked to provide your name, e-mail address, postal address, and more information, if needed.
For purchases from e-Node's website, you are required to fill out certain fields in the order form that is primarily for e-Node website's internal use. Depending on e-Node website's contractual agreement with the publisher of the software you downloaded, e-Node may provide your personal information to that publisher, not including your credit card information. Aside from providing this information to the publisher of the software you download, e-Node does not and will not provide your personal information to any other party. You may choose to support or not to support registration for products you download from e-node.net.
Contact information from the order form is used to send orders and information about our company to our customers. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the Opt-Out/Modify/Delete section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services.
Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their e-mail address) and demographic information (like their zip code, or age). We may use contact data from our surveys to send the user information about our company. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the Opt-Out/Modify/Delete section below.
Updating Your Personal Information
You have the right to access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences. This may be accomplished by either logging into your account on e-Node's website and accessing your information, or by writing to e-Node SARL:
e-Node SARL
Attn: Customer Service
177 cours de l'Argonne
33000 Bordeaux
France
Please include your name, address, and/or e-mail address when you contact us. Please note that e-Node is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non-e-Node Web sites to which e-node.net or any other e-Node Web site may link.
Opt-Out/Modify/Delete
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us, modify their information in our database, or be deleted from our database all together. Please e-mail requests to webmaster@e-node.net.
Use of Cookies
e-Node Web sites primarily use cookies to allow users to choose a default e-Node global site.
When you visit the e-Node's website Web site, we place a text file called a ''cookie'' in the browser directory of your computer's hard drive. A cookie is a small piece of information that a Web site can store on your Web browser and later retrieve. The cookie cannot be read by any Web site other than the one that wrote the cookie. The cookie enables this Web site to recognize the information you have consented to give and functions as your identification card, recording your passwords, purchases, and preferences. As a result, cookies will allow you to retrieve previous search results, access various areas with ease, and view your previous invoices. It cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.
The cookie is used to track your visit to e-node.net and will automatically log the IP/Internet address of your computer, this information does not identify you personally and you remain anonymous unless you have otherwise provided e-Node's website with personal information. We do NOT use cookies to examine your surfing behavior before or after leaving the e-Node's website Web site.
If at any time you believe that e-Node's website has not followed the above policy, or if you would like your information to be removed from our system, notify the e-Node's website Webmaster and all reasonable efforts to identify and correct any problem will be made.
Security
Our sites intend to secure your personal information with the highest level of Internet security. e-Node's website uses the latest in secure server technology to protect orders. When you shop at e-Node's website, you will have the option to use our secure server for placing your order, if your browser supports secure server transactions. Our secure server software (SSL) encrypts all of your personal information including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet.
If you prefer not to provide your credit card number over the Internet, you can opt to place your order via fax or telephone.
Business Relationships
This site contains links to other sites. e-Node SARL. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
AreaList ProPrintList ProInternet ToolKitCalendarSetSuperReport Pro
Third parties
Zip4DOle4D
Oldies
SanityCheckDataCheckDisplayListSerial ToolKit4D Line
Development v17
4D Developer Standard4D Developer Professional4D Team Developer Professional - 2 Users4D Team Developer Expansion - 1 User
Deployment v17
4D Server - 2 Users4D Client Expansion4D Write Pro Expansion4D View Pro Expansion4D Web Application Expansion - Unlimited4D Web Services Expansion - Unlimited4D Web Application Expansion for 4D Client - Unlimited - 1 User4D Web Services Expansion for 4D Client - Unlimited - 1 User4D for OCI Expansion - 1 User4D ODBC Pro Expansion - 1 User4D SQL Desktop
Development v18
4D Developer Standard4D Developer Professional4D Team Developer Expansion - 1 User4D Team Developer Professional - 2 Users
Deployment v18
4D Server - 2 Users4D Client Expansion4D Write Pro Expansion4D View Pro Expansion4D Web Application Expansion - Unlimited4D Web Services Expansion - Unlimited4D Web Application Expansion for 4D Client - Unlimited - 1 User4D Web Services Expansion for 4D Client - Unlimited - 1 User4D for OCI Expansion - 1 User4D ODBC Pro Expansion - 1 User4D SQL DesktopPDF Printer 4D PluginPDF-ToolsPDF-XChange Standard PrinterPDF-XChange EditorPDF-XChange Editor PlusPDF-XChange PRO
This website uses cookies to ensure you get the best experience.
By using this site you agree to the use of cookies.
